https://www.atc.org.au/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
ATC respects the privacy of everyone who visits our website and anyone about whom we have personal information.
Any personal information we have about you will be used by us to provide you with information about ATC, Tibet, ongoing campaigns, lobbying, other awareness-raising activities and events and our merchandise. You may be contacted by mail, phone or e-mail, unless you ask us not to do so.
Any information we collect will be as provided by you and at no time will we sell your information. The personal information you supply through our site will be securely stored.
You are able to access other websites by clicking on links we have provided on our website. You should be aware that we are not responsible for these other sites. You may need to check their privacy policies and practices, which may not be the same as our own.
Cookies are small pieces of data that our site can send to your web browser. Cookies do not capture any private information. We use cookies to:
Keep track of advertisements.
Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services, such as Google Analytics, that track this information on our behalf. You can control cookies in your browser settings.
We have the right to change this statement at any time and notify you by publishing a new version of this statement on our website.
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, please get in touch via our contact form.
